export const data = [
    {
      question: "Who is made King after King Viserys’ death?",
      option1: "Aegon II Targaryen",
      option2: "Rhaenyra Targaryen",
      option3: "Daemon Targaryen",
      option4: "Aemond Targaryen",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What does Valar Morghulis mean?",
      option1: "All men must serve",
      option2: "All men must fight",
      option3: "All men must forgive",
      option4: "All men must die",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the actual father of Jacaerys Valaryon?",
      option1: "Harwin Strong",
      option2: "Laenor Valaryon",
      option3: "Sir Criston cole",
      option4: "Daemon Targaryen",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Name 1 of Daenerys Targaryen’s dragons?",
      option1: "Moondancer",
      option2: "Meleys",
      option3: "Rhaegal",
      option4: "Seasmoke",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Which dragon was Unclaimed?",
      option1: "Caraxes",
      option2: "Cannibal",
      option3: "Silverwing",
      option4: "Drogon",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which city does King Viserys build a sculpture of as a hobby?",
      option1: "Dragonstone",
      option2: "King's Landing",
      option3: "Old Town",
      option4: "Old Valyria",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What is Jamie Lannisters nickname?",
      option1: "Little Finger",
      option2: "The Hound",
      option3: "Queenslayer",
      option4: "Kingslayer",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Which dragon killed Vhagar?",
      option1: "Caraxes",
      option2: "Vermithor",
      option3: "Meleys",
      option4: "Silverwing",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is Hodor’s real name?",
      option1: "Reed",
      option2: "Wylis",
      option3: "Jon",
      option4: "Rickon",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Who will be king after Daenerys Targaryen?",
      option1: "Jon Snow",
      option2: "Jaehaerys III Targaryen",
      option3: "Bran Stark",
      option4: "Tyrion Lannister",
      ans: 3,
    },
  ];